jit.su 2013-04-01

# Privacy - Nodejitsu

Nodejitsu, Inc. (“Nodejitsu,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Nodejitsu when you use the Nodejitsu Service, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. Our basic principles are:

  * We won't spam you or sell your personal information to others.

  * You control how we send most messages to you.

  * You control who you share your Applications with.

  * We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will only collect, use, and share your information as we describe in this Privacy Policy or as you give us express permission to do. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.

### Information We Collect

**User-Provided Information:** You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register for an account with the Service. You also provide us information in the Content and Application(s) you post to the Service. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. If you sign up for a paid subscription to the Service, we will ask you for your credit card information, which we store in encrypted form.

**Cookies Information:** When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Nodejitsu help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey anonymous information about how you browse the Service to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log File Information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

### How We Use Your Information

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.

By providing Nodejitsu your email address, you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out or change your preferences in your "My Account page".

Following termination or deactivation of your account, Nodejitsu may retain your profile information, Content, and Application for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes. Furthermore, Nodejitsu may retain and continue to use indefinitely all Content contained in your communications to other users or posted to public or semi-public areas of the Service after termination or deactivation of your account.

If you choose to use our invitation service to invite a friend to the Service, we will ask you for that person's email address and automatically send an email invitation. Nodejitsu stores this information to send this email, to register your friend if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our invitation service. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database at privacy@Nodejitsu.com.

Nodejitsu may use certain information about you and/or your Application internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

Nodejitsu reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor or remove the Content you post on the Service if in our sole opinion such Content violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Service, or to protect or defend our rights or property or those of any third party. Nodejitsu also reserves the right to remove Content upon the request of any third party.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Service; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as activity, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (h) track Content and users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

### How We Share Your Information

Personally Identifiable Information: Nodejitsu will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. Nodejitsu may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing the Service to you (for instance, to process your credit card transactions). If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Nodejitsu (for instance, on servers in the cloud).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

If you invite another user to share your Application, we will share the Application and associated Content with that user. You can change your Application sharing settings at any time in you app resource page. Any Content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to public areas of the Service becomes available to the public. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other users have copied or saved that information.

By subscribing to or enabling an Add-on, you grant Nodejitsu permission to share your Application, Content, and user information with the Add-on Provider as necessary in order to provide you the Add-on. We cannot control third parties’ use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with an Add-on Provider, you can choose not to subscribe to or enable Add-ons.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Nodejitsu will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Nodejitsu, our users or others.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Nodejitsu services.

### How We Protect Your Information

Nodejitsu uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information and implement your Application sharing settings.  We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Nodejitsu or store on the Service, and you do so at your own risk.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

### Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Nodejitsu will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

### Your Choices About Your Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Service, in which case Nodejitsu may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account on [http://nodejitsu.com](http://nodejitsu.com/). You can review and correct the information about you that Nodejitsu keeps on file by contacting us directly at support@nodejitsu.com.

### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Nodejitsu does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Members. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on Nodejitsu. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@nodejitsu.com.

### Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

### Notification Procedures

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by Nodejitsu in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Service to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at privacy@nodejitsu.com, or send mail to: Nodejitsu, Inc., Privacy, 135 E 27th Street, New York, NY, 10016.
